Picking up speed nicely.
She's ahead of the leader now,
on pace for a top time.
It's a fantastic day here at
Areskatan Mountain
for day two of the 2019
Alpine Skiing Grande Prix.
Today is the lady's super G.
Here we go, it's a quick drop.
Not much of a jump.
Ooh, really hugging
the gate here,
that's gonna add to her time.
We'll see whether it's
enough to sink her,
or if she can come back
with a strong finish
down the Dragon's Back.
Nice turns here,
her confidence really showing.
And she's already
ahead of the leader,
skiing very well through
the middle section,
keeping her speed.
A great performance from
the American, Emily Garner,
in a quest for a second gold.
What a come-back story
that would be
after the heartbreaking injury
that caused her to miss Sochi
four years ago...
Now, I think
there can definitely be
some speed down here
to make up for her rocky start.
But she's running out of room.
Coming to the final turn
up ahead...
keeping great form, skis tight,
checking the inside gate...
this is the approach that's been
tough for her competitors
yesterday
where everyone
dropped off the pace.
Will it cost her the same time?
Just a tenth of a second
is more than she can afford.
She's still in the medals
by 5/100 of a second,
but she needs to get through
this combination right
without taking the turn
too wide.
And here she comes to
the final pattern.
Coming up to the key turn.
Here it comes now and
she gets her line right.
This could be our best new time.
Now, this is known as
Magic Valley, it will be...
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Doesn't look like nothing.
I got another gig, okay?
So you were just gonna leave?
I was gonna call you
from the road.
You're not leaving until you
tell me what is going on.
I just told you.
The cab's gonna be here
any minute.
He can wait.
And she's done it!
What a great performance
from the American.
Can you please shut that off?
All the way from...
I was going to
right after her run.
No, I don't care, okay?
I just want to go.
I'm on a schedule.
Okay. Then I'll drive you.
You don't need to drive me.
You know you can tell me
anything, right?
Stop putting your shoes on.
I saw your deposits.
4200?
I got paid.
You were paid a third of that.
I saw the listing, honey.
- Is it a sugar daddy?
- Oh, Jesus Christ, Mom...
Or if it's one of those
OnlyFans things,
I will just say this:
It lasts forever, Sophie.
He's here.
And it's called
getting a tip, okay?
If the owners get back home
and the place isn't trashed
or their pets aren't dead,
then they pull out
another wad of cash.
Can I go?
Thank you.
That's a hell of a tip.
Yeah, well, they're rich.
What do you want?
You think it's charity.
I didn't say that.
I'm sorry. Look, just...
Let me drive you, it's silly
to waste money on a cab.
I'm not, the owner is.
Do you have everything?
Gloves? Hat?
Yes.
Can I have a hug at least?
Come here.
I worry. Okay?
One day, you won't
hold that against me.
I'm gonna be late.
Yeah.
Be safe.
Hey, sweetie. You okay?
Can I call you back?
You were supposed to call me
when you got there.
I hadn't heard from you,
so I got worried.
I'm fine. I'm almost there.
Okay. You have
your charger, right?
You know you can call me
if you need anything.
- Mom.
- Okay, okay, just last thing.
Check my email.
There's this new app
I heard about
and it could be...
handy in case you need...
- Okay, I'll check it out.
- No, really, I think...
I think it's perfect for you,
sweetie.
- If you get stuck and...
- Hello? Mom?
You're breaking up. We must be
in the mountains or something.
Well, I hear you fine.
How about now?
- Hello?
- Sophie?
Hello, Mom?
I'll call you back, okay?
Can you hear...
I got bars if you want mine.
I'm good.
- Can I take these for you?
- I got it. Thanks.
Okay.
Uh, where's the front door?
Oh, it's just... it's just...
You... Just tell me.
Yeah, right there,
straight ahead.
Okay.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
There's, uh...
There's just a little step...
Yep. I got it.
Okay.
- Sophie. Hi.
- Hi.
Uh, please come in.
Come in. Uh...
- Yep, this way.
- Okay.
- You good?
- Yeah. Sorry I'm a bit late.
Um, would you mind
grabbing my bags for me?
I'll be right back
in a second, okay?
Thank you.
All right, so I'll make it quick
because I'm late for my flight.
The security system code is
7-4-2-6-7.
- Do you need me to show you?
- I'll get it.
Okay. So job number one.
Archie. Come here, baby,
come to Mama.
Oh, uh, careful 'cause
he's allergic to...
Gluten. Yeah.
I called your vet before I left.
That is so great.
And here I was, worried.
Why?
Oh. No, I just mean...
everything was so last minute,
you know,
and you were the only one
that responded in time
on the website.
So, uh, what's the occasion,
business or pleasure?
Uh, pleasure.
Fresh off a divorce.
Filled out the paperwork
yesterday.
Sorry to hear that.
Oh, don't be.
If anything, it was a good
training ground, you know?
I married older for maturity,
not for money.
Found out he has neither.
That was great.
Uh, anyway, look.
All of Archie's food
is in the pantry.
I can show you where it is.
No, I'll find it. Thanks.
Okay, just do me a favor.
Don't overdo the treats.
Um, his box and his toys
are in the den.
And, oh, yes. The breaker box
and the thermostat
are in the utility room
next to the laundry room.
And the guest room's all ready
for you, just down the hall.
- Why don't I show you?
- No, that's okay, I'll find it.
Of course, you will.
Well, you have my number, so...
Archie, honey, Mommy will be
home soon, okay?
Ciao.
Have a safe flight.
Monitor.
Video call, Cam.
- Hey!
- What's up, loser?
How's the crib?
You tell me.
Uh, high ceilings.
Skylight.
Marble floors.
Bougie as fuck.
Better be. I didn't come
all the way out here
for a log cabin.
Can I go straight, this way?
- Yes, you can.
- Yeah?
Um, you have a footstool
coming up ahead.
- Okay.
- Three feet and closing,
step to your left.
- Good?
- You're good.
We got a deerskin rug.
Post-modern chandelier.
Lots of wood. Chalet vibes.
I heard my voice traveling.
Yeah, there's an open partition.
Kitchen, and through that
a family room, I guess.
Oh, head's up. You got a...
a wall just ahead of you.
Big painting on it.
Anything famous?
What am I, cultured?
You really shouldn't
take it for granted.
Okay, kitchen ahead.
The island is on your right.
Two steps.
Okay, you're good.
You're in the kitchen.
Uh, you got some couches.
Fireplace.
And floor to ceiling windows
with a great view.
View of what?
Nothing. Just nature.
Okay, on your left,
you have, um, stairs leading to
what looks like an open room.
And a... a hallway.
Pick one.
Hallway.
Okay, you've got some stairs
ahead of you.
Railing's on your left.
- Careful.
- I'm fine.
Okay, you're reaching the end
to a landing.
And you're there.
What's over here?
Looks like a greenhouse.
Plants everywhere,
like a solarium, I guess.
Cool.
Oh, wait. Another set of
stairs. Careful.
It's too dark, I can't see.
Flashlight.
- Good?
- Good.
You got a narrow hallway with
a few doors on your right.
Okay.
Pantry.
Water heater.
Cam?
Hello?
Poor connection.
Soph, you there?
Yeah, sorry, I had a bad
connection for a second.
What's this?
Wine cellar.
Sweet.
What do we got?
Uh, Chambertin Grand Cru, 1989.
I don't hear any Googling.
$4500.
Perfect. Still petty.
You should put it back.
She's not gonna miss one.
I told you,
I can't keep doing this.
You're not, you're just...
pointing the way.
Then I walk out with it,
then list it.
And then I help you sell it.
You couldn't do it without me
and that makes me
just as guilty.
Last place was two grand,
it was three before that.
I only went along
'cause I thought
you needed the money.
You think being blind
is gonna save you?
Yeah. It always saves me.
You'd know that if you saw
how they treated me.
You walk out with it, I'm done.
What does that mean?
You know the last time
we talked...
the last house... a month ago...
Yeah, what the fuck else are we
supposed to talk about?
The fact that you're on a hill
right now and I'm not?
You could be, right behind me.
Okay, well, why don't you
go down a mountain
at 110 blindfolded
and then talk to me.
You have the courage
to rob a house
but not to let me guide you
down a hill?
Fuck you!
Are you putting it back or not?
Don't worry, I can't do it
without you, right?
Soph...
From Paralympics USA.
Subject, Reminder:
Deadline for upcoming
qualifications...
- Delete.
- Message deleted.
From Mom. Subject: See For Me.
How cool is this? Love you, Mom.
See For Me.
A new app for the blind
and visually impaired.
Connect to a sighted helper
on demand
for visual assistance
in a live video call.
- Delete.
- Message deleted.
I put it back, all right?
Put what back?
Nothing. Hi, Debra.
Hey, uh, so listen.
I'm just checking in.
Just wanted to see if
you, uh... you fed Archie.
- Yep.
- Great.
And did you arm
the security system?
I was just about to.
Why don't we do that together?
It would just make me feel
a lot better.
Absolutely.
Sophie?
We could video call
if that helps.
Uh, no, I got it, I'm good.
Okay.
System armed.
There. All good.
You're great.
Call me if you
need anything. Okay?
- Sure thing, Debra.
- Bye.
Fuck.
Call Ca...
Apps.
Download See For Me.
Downloading See For Me.
Open See For Me.
Welcome to See For Me.
Select "I am blind"
or "I am sighted."
I am blind.
See For Me would like to access
your camera and microphone.
Allow.
Tap screen twice to connect
to first available helper.
Creating request.
Connecting to servers.
One moment.
Hello. I'm Maeve.
How can I help you?
Yeah, I locked myself out.
Do you see a way
to get back inside?
Oh, you poor thing.
The handle is right in front
of you if you just step...
No, I know where the handle is,
it's locked.
I guess you and I
are just gonna have to pay
a little visit to the neighbors
and call a locksmith.
The nearest house is, like...
- You know what? Thanks, Maeve.
- Okay...
Tap once
for next available helper.
Eyes open, people.
Take the higher ground on
the right, use your cover.
Let's get these motherfuckers.
Go, go! Watch your six!
Watch your left flank,
we got one on the roof.
Bunch of bullshit. Yo! Back up!
Dark, Dark, what are you doing?
Get back to cover! Oh, fuck!
Ah, motherfucker had
a rocket launcher. Fuck!
Great.
Are you guys gonna
listen to me next time,
or are we just gonna keep
getting our asses kicked?
- Oh, please.
- Fuck off!
Jesus Christ. Chill!
Taking five. You guys are
on your own.
Hey, what can I do for you?
Hi, I'm locked out.
Do you see a way
I can get back in?
Uh, is there somebody
that you could call?
I'm talking to you, aren't I?
Uh, you are because
you called me.
Hold on a second here.
All right, can you
show me around a little bit?
Uh...
just slowly pan
from left to right.
Yeah, I don't see
an easy way in.
I think you might have to
call the cops.
I knew this was a waste of time.
Look, my last call on here
was telling a guy
the expiration date
on his milk, okay?
This isn't exactly
routine for me.
Now, do you want to
get in or not?
Yeah, I just...
I just want to do it myself.
Copy.
Okay, uh...
do you know if there's any
unlocked doors or windows,
preferably on the ground floor?
I don't know.
This isn't my house,
I'm just cat sitting.
Okay. Uh, let's move around
the perimeter.
Can you angle your phone
at 9:00?
- Over here?
- Good.
Okay, you're okay.
Keep going.
You're doing great.
Okay, good,
now just hug the wall.
Good.
Great, keep going.
Yep. All right, now you're at
a set of stairs.
There's six steps and
a railing on your right.
Good.
All right, down another.
You're doing great.
Okay, at the bottom of
the steps,
there's a walkway about 40 feet
and there's
nothing ahead of you.
Great.
Can you hold the phone steady?
It's just shaking a bit.
Yeah, I'm freezing and
I don't have my cane
so I can't go up steps fast.
I... I hear you but I still
need to see, all right?
You're doing fine,
just... just go slow.
All right? And take your time.
Uh, okay, stop there.
Angle the phone down a bit.
Oh... Split the difference.
Little bit too much.
All right, you're right in front
of a sliding glass door.
Can you feel it?
It's locked.
Yeah, but there's no rod
so this could work.
So you're gonna need
two hands for this,
so can you put your phone
on the ground?
Seriously?
Trust me, all right?
You're gonna put one hand
on the handle,
and you're gonna place
your other hand
firmly on the glass pane.
You're gonna push in,
and you're gonna rock the door
up and down, up and down.
All right?
We're gonna try to
dislodge it from the track.
[Sophie grunting.
It's not working.
Just trust me. Keep going.
Up and down and to the left.
Okay, what the hell
are we doing here?
Uh, I'm helping
a stubborn blind girl
break into a house that
may or may not be hers.
How about you?
Yeah, well, I'm down on my
hands and knees
getting trolled by
some random...
You were saying?
No shit.
Oh, shit!
Hey, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Oh... Plant, 12:00.
Oh, shit!
Twelve o'clock means
right ahead of you.
You're good. To the right,
to the right to the right.
Okay, keep going, there's
stairs in front of you.
Right, right there. Yeah.
Okay, a few more.
Keep going, try to
hold the phone steady.
Okay, there's stairs
to your left.
Yeah, it's right ahead of you.
Okay, good, good, good.
Up, up, up, up. Up.
System disarmed.
Yes!
Mission accomplished.
Nice trick.
Most people wouldn't be
so quick to...
help a stranger
break into a house.
Well, I didn't exactly
take you for a criminal,
if that's what you're saying.
Or, wait. Am I now
an accessory to a B and E?
You don't sound
too worried about that.
Yeah, well, I've done worse.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
Uh, no, I'm good.
Thank you.
Kelly.
Thanks, Kelly.
My name's Sophie.
Be careful, Sophie.
Tap once to report or save user.
Tap twice to make another call.
Report this user or
save as a priority.
Save as priority.
The guide's job is to be
the eyes of
the visually impaired skier.
Straight.
Up, up, up. Half left.
The relationship
of skier and guide
is as important as the skiing
ability of the athlete.
Training is focused on
calls and responses.
The guide you...
The relationship of
skier and guide
is as important as the skiing
ability of the athlete.
Straight.
Up, up, up. Half left.
Training is focused on
calls and responses.
We're good.
System disarmed.
Monitor.
Come on.
Hey. Hey! Quiet.
What is it?
We've got a problem.
I think someone's here.
What? What the hell
are you talkin' about?
Stick to the plan.
Until we hear from him.
All right.
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
There's people in the house.
I'm at Six Golden Lane.
Okay. Do they know
you're in the house?
I think so.
And did you see the intruders?
I'm blind, but I heard them
and their in the house,
I'm sure of it.
Okay, stay calm.
Help is on the way.
How long?
Given your location,
I can't be sure exactly
but I'll be here with you
the whole time.
How the fuck is that
supposed to help me?
I'm getting out of here now.
Ma'am, just stay calm.
Help is on the...
Call Cam.
See For Me.
Hey, how can I help you?
It's me, Sophie.
Sophie.
Wait, what's wrong?
There's people in the house.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I heard them,
I heard their voices.
What's your location?
I'll call the cops.
No, I already did that.
Okay, um...
Just stay calm.
Stay exactly where you are,
let them take
whatever they want.
I think they're looking for me.
How many of them are there?
At least two.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure, there's
two different voices.
Okay, Sophie,
where are they now?
Close.
Sophie.
You're too exposed,
we need to get you to
the basement,
somewhere where you can hide
until the cops get there.
And trap myself down there?
No, I need to
get out of here now.
Okay, just go slowly,
keep panning.
I need to see angles
before we move, okay?
All right,
you're coming to a turn.
Stop.
Let me see.
All right.
You've got one guy
in the foyer
past the door on the far wall.
No, no, no, you can't go
back that way.
No, the other guy's there.
Show me the wall.
Oh, door, 10:00.
Okay, bring your phone up
and then pan
left to right for me.
Okay.
We got one guy drilling,
facing the wall.
That hallway at 11:00
goes away from both of them.
If you stay down,
you can make it.
I know where the front door is.
I'm gonna go for it.
No, no, Sophie. Not the door.
Shit!
Ten o'clock.
- Hey.
- Yeah, you know what?
This would go a lot faster
if I had some help.
Yeah. Well, there's
definitely someone here.
What?
You're early.
There's someone else
in the house.
Impossible.
There's someone here.
Search it,
room by room, top to bottom.
Copy.
Keep drilling.
I'm sweeping the place.
Hey, hey, hey.
If someone's here,
we're not supposed to be.
He said the place was gonna be
fuckin' empty.
He said keep drilling.
Fuck.
Okay, come on.
He's drilling again.
Is the other one gone?
I think so, just... just
hold there a second.
I'm going for it.
No, no, no, Sophie...
Sophie, just slow down,
I need to see.
Wait. Sophie, wait!
Sophie!
Sophie.
Sophie! Sophie, can you hear me?
Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey!
Hey!
Shut your fuckin' mouth.
What the hell
are you doing, man?
Shh!
Go get her things.
They're in the bedroom.
Speak.
She dialed 9-1-112 minutes ago.
Response time?
We timed it at 22,
19 to be safe,
that gives us... seven.
Let her go.
Who are you?
Just take what you want and go,
I won't say anything.
What are you doing here?
Cat sitting.
- Six minutes.
- Yeah.
We need to go. We gotta go.
Please, this wasn't the plan.
No one's going anywhere.
We need to off her right now.
You can just go.
I don't know anything.
She's seen our faces.
No, I haven't!
I'm blind.
ID.
Sophie Scott.
"Hm." The diagnosis of
retinitis pigmentosa
dashes the Olympic dreams of
top under-18 female skier."
Bring me in close.
There's nothin' left in there.
No.
Just light perception.
No shit.
All right, pack it up,
make it spotless.
Tail lights in two.
Just gonna leave her here?
She's not a problem.
- Four minutes.
- But she knows.
No names, no faces.
She's useless.
No offense, Sophie.
When she tells the cops
we were here,
it's game over.
And if she goes missing?
Lost blind girl in the woods?
They'll comb the property
for weeks.
But you said
you're the only other person
who knows that it's here.
We should go because we could
always come back.
It won't still be here if we do.
Do you want to kiss
7 million goodbye?
We have no time.
It's a risk we have to take.
He's right.
We need to go now, guys.
It's tonight or it's never.
It's that fuckin' simple.
What choice do we fuckin' have?
- The cops'll be there...
- I can do it.
I can get rid of the cops.
I'll say it was a mistake.
And why would you do that?
I want an equal share.
I'm listening.
And I want you to prove
you won't hurt me.
I told you,
you are not a witness.
Just say it. All of it.
Say what?
I get rid of the cops,
then...
Then we finish
and give you your share.
Five percent.
Ten, 15 minutes,
then we're done.
And you'll never see...
You'll never hear from us again.
What about Debra?
When she gets back,
she's gonna know.
It will look like
we were never here.
You don't have to
worry about her.
Just leave when you're
supposed to.
What if the cops come and
she changes her mind.
I won't.
How do we know that?
Look in my bag.
4500 retail.
I was gonna sell it for three.
No, no you didn't.
Who's gonna suspect
the little blind girl, right?
Three minutes.
Make the call.
On speaker, please.
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
I, uh...
Hello?
My name is Sophie Scott.
I'm at Six Golden Lane.
I called earlier and reported
a home invasion.
It was a false alarm.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I made a mistake.
There's no one here.
I'm blind. I thought
I heard something,
but I forgot I left the TV on.
It's stupid, I know.
I'm glad to hear
everything's okay, Sophie.
An officer will be
arriving shortly
to check in and confirm.
But I just said I'm fine,
I don't need anyone.
It's required by law that
we send a responder,
even if it's a mistake.
They'll be there soon.
Is there anything else
I can do for you, ma'am?
No. No, that's it. Thanks.
Fuck.
It's not my fault.
I didn't know they were g...
Relax, you did great.
They were never gonna
turn around.
You just set it up.
Now is when you nail it.
You can do that, right, Sophie?
- I can do it.
- You sure?
Last chance to back out.
If you think it's too much...
I said I can fucking do it.
Good.
O, get back to your perch,
give us a head's up.
D, move all of the equipment
into the vehicles.
And E, lights off.
Scott.
Sierra, Charlie, Oscar,
Tango, Tango.
Now, you said
you've never met her?
I was just talking to her.
Look.
How many blind, female,
teenage ex skiers
do you think there are?
This has to be her.
Ma'am, I understand
your distress,
but I can't forward this to
another department
without knowing her location.
Look, her last Twitter post
puts her in New York. Okay?
She's in a rural mansion,
likely upstate,
and she's already made a
9-1-1 call for a home invasion.
You need to get a hold of
every department north of NYC
to cross check that call,
and let them know there are
three hostiles, minimum.
On site, one car.
Copy.
Sophie, listen to me.
Don't shake him off like
the guy who grabs your arm
on the subway.
Let them think they helped,
so they can walk the fuck out
happy with themselves.
You got it?
Comin' up the driveway,
one minute.
Copy that.
You good?
Police.
Hello?
Hello. This is Deputy Brooks
from the Sheriff's station.
Who am I speaking with?
Sophie.
You mind opening the door
for me, Sophie?
I... I made a mistake,
I called back and explained it.
It was just an accident.
You accidentally called 9-1-1
and reported a home invasion?
Yeah,
I thought I heard something
and I overreacted.
Could you open the door, please?
I'm not allowed to.
Says who?
Debra. The homeowner.
She hired me to
look after her house,
and she said
I shouldn't let anyone in.
I'm a police officer.
Sophie, one way or another,
I'm coming inside.
Hi.
Evening.
Like I said,
it was just a mistake.
Okay.
I'll be out of your hair
in no time.
House sitting, huh?
Cat sitting, actually.
I'm more of
a dog person, myself.
Still beats sitting in
a car all night.
It's nice and warm in here.
Good place to hide out
from this cold front.
So, you want to give me
the grand tour?
There's not much to see.
That was a joke.
You said you heard voices?
Uh, yeah, I... I forgot
I left the TV on.
You mistook the TV for
people in the house?
I also might have been
a little drunk.
It's a big house.
Is it possible maybe
someone did break in,
but then they left when they
realized you were here?
No.
What's going on here?
What?
You got a panel loose.
There's a fire hazard here.
Oh...
Okay, I'll let Debra know.
I guess I'll get going, then.
Drive safe.
Sophie.
Is it possible that maybe
someone was here,
but there's a reason
you have to lie about it?
No.
Maybe they're still close by.
You think I wanted to bring you
all the way out here
just so I can
embarrass myself like this?
Please.
I'm just trying to help.
I don't need any help.
Okay.
Take care.
That your phone?
Yeah.
You wanna get it?
No, it's not...
- Let me grab it for you.
- No, it's okay, um...
It's a big house.
Wouldn't want
you to lose it in here.
Thanks.
You gonna answer it or what?
No, it's...
Might be important.
Hello?
Uh, yeah, pocket dial. Sorry.
No, it's okay.
Look, Cam, sorry,
I really gotta go.
We good, officer?
Yeah.
We're good.
Sorry to bring you
all the way out here.
Hey, shit happens. Right?
Dispatch to Victor One.
Go for Victor.
Have a good night, Sophie.
Be advised, we got
a call about your 2-11
forwarded from
a Florida precinct.
A woman there says
she was on a video chat
with the 9-1-1 caller
during the incident.
They give a description?
At least three perpetrators.
She saw one of them,
white male, mid 30s,
dressed in black.
Dispatch, was there
a description of the girl?
A blind girl, Sophie.
Stay back.
I'm sorry.
Where are they?
I don't know.
Coming out.
Hands where I can see them!
It's just me, it's only me.
- I... I'm not resisting.
- Get on the ground.
Now!
- How many of you?
- It's just me.
Sophie, how many?
Dispatch, this is Victor One.
I need back up at
Six Golden Lane.
Just take me in. It's only me.
Sophie.
I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Where are they?
There's two more of them but
I don't know where they are.
Stop!
Ahh!
Oh, fuck.
Jesus Christ.
She was gonna arrest me
for a fucking B and E.
Dave could have finished.
I'd have been out in six months.
- Fuck.
- It's a fucking misdemeanor!
You never said anything
about this, man, this is fucked!
Hey. You good?
Yeah.
Where's the girl?
No, wait.
Get me out of these things.
Dave.
- Dave!
- Fuck.
Get back to the safe.
We've got 20 minutes before
her back up gets here.
Where's her gun?
Sophie, Sophie, are you okay?
They killed a cop.
Where are you?
I'm getting out of here.
No, no, no, no,
just hold on a second.
Where are they now?
I can't help you if you don't...
You got a gun?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what are you doing?
No, no, no, don't go outside,
you'll be a sitting duck
out there.
Sophie, listen to me.
Is there anything in my way?
It's rough terrain,
it's open ground,
and it's too dark.
I can't see for you
if you're out here.
- You're not gonna make it.
- Yes, I will!
Sophie, they're gonna kill you.
Please listen to me.
I swear we can do this.
You just need to trust me.
What should I do?
Bingo.
Okay, careful.
It's too dark for me
to see clearly.
Okay, go slowly.
Okay, I think you're clear
but I can't see the ground.
Can you pan for me?
Sophie, Sophie, are you okay?
I lost the gun.
Show me the ground.
Flashlight.
Okay. Two o'clock.
Yeah, almost. Good, good.
They're drilling again.
Okay, but that's just one,
we need to assume
the other two are still
looking for you, okay?
So you have to stand up.
Flashlight.
What is it?
Someone's coming.
Soft-shoed guy.
You have eyes on her?
Hold the gun out.
I want you to feel on the side
for a little knob,
and tell me if it's up or down.
Uh, it's down.
Okay, good, that means
the safety's off.
He's in the room.
It's okay.
Let him get
a little closer to you.
Hold the phone steady.
- She came in...
- Now!
- Sophie.
- Adjust left.
Split the difference.
- Inhale.
- What are you doing?
And on my mark...
fire on your exhale.
Sophie, it's okay.
Just relax.
Fire!
Everything's okay.
Sophie, shoot him.
Okay, he's coming closer to you.
- Sophie.
- Don't come any closer.
To the right.
Adjust right.
Sophie,
he's getting closer to you.
It's fine. You're fine.
We'll make... We'll make
something work,
just, uh, put the gun down.
Adjust left, up, up.
Split the difference and fire.
Fire.
Sophie!
No one's gonna hurt you.
Sophie, he's got a knife.
Sophie, he's coming toward you.
Fire now!
Sophie?
Sophie!
Sophie.
Yeah.
Okay. Okay, he's down.
We need to keep moving.
They probably heard
the gunshots.
Low battery. Twenty percent.
Where's your charger?
In my bag by the door.
No, it's too exposed.
You have to keep moving.
- Wait, watch...
- Stairs. I know.
Adjust right. Fire!
- Kelly?
- Sophie.
- Poor connection.
- Sophie?
Kelly? Kelly, where are you?
Sophie, can you hear me?
Uh, left. Fire!
Hold.
He's dead.
Okay, get his radio
on his waist.
Now take a minute.
The other one's... upstairs.
I need to move.
No, I can hear
that he's still drilling.
You're in a good position, okay?
Just... Just take a second...
and breathe.
- Breathe.
- I am fucking breathing.
No, you're not.
Through your nose.
Like you're at the top of
the ski slope before a run.
You're gonna inhale...
hold it for a second...
and exhale.
How did you know I used to ski?
Top ten best skiers
under 18 in the country.
Pretty impressive.
I haven't skied in years.
Yeah, what's your excuse?
Well, for starters,
I live in Florida.
Low battery.
Ten percent.
Kelly.
Yeah, I heard.
All right, listen.
There's only one left,
and the cops are almost there.
All right, you just need to keep
camping out down there.
One way in and one way out.
And you're gonna
hold your gun on it. Copy?
Copy.
Why do you talk
like you're in the Army?
Twenty-second infantry.
Combat engineers.
Iraq?
Yeah.
And now I'm behind a desk
on admin duty.
You make it sound like
a punishment.
It is.
And I deserve it.
Is it worse than
getting a cop killed?
You can't be sorry you called
the cops, Sophie.
I was working with them.
I told them I could
get rid of the cops if...
they gave me an equal share.
I could have told her.
I could have left with her.
I shouldn't even be here.
Yeah, no shit.
No, I mean these bullshit jobs.
Should be out on the slopes
training.
You can ski blind?
People can, yeah.
If you have
years of training and...
a guide that you trust
with your life.
Come on. Yeah.
There we go. We're in.
Guys?
Guys, where are ya?
Low battery. Five percent.
I'm gonna lose you any minute.
All right.
We have two options.
One: You can square up
on the stairs,
wait for the cops to arrive.
But I need you to tell me
where to shoot.
No, if he's dumb enough to
come down that way,
you'll be able to get him
without me.
What's option two?
- Speak.
- I need two more minutes.
Ernie and Otis are MIA.
You want to elaborate on that?
I don't know where they are.
They're not answering.
They went after the girl.
Just get it done.
Call me when you're leaving.
Understood.
All right,
his back is toward you,
he can't see you.
Okay, keep going.
Little closer.
All right, square up,
plant your feet on the ground.
Adjust right.
Fire!
Jesus!
- Hey.
- Down! Adjust left!
- Stop! Please!
- Fire!
- Sophie, fire.
- Don't, don't, don't!
Just let me go.
No, don't listen to him.
He's just trying to stall.
Sophie, I'm gonna lose you.
You need to fire.
- He's right in front of you.
- Please.
Sophie, shoot him,
you've got him.
It's open.
You can take what you want,
you can have it all,
just let me go.
You're gonna lose me. Shoot him.
Shoot him!
He said the house
was gonna be empty.
I never would have
signed up for this shit
if I knew you were
gonna be here.
Sophie, you're gonna lose...
Please, just let me go.
Sophie! Sophie.
Shit! Shit!
Don't move.
We wait for the cops.
I said don't move!
I'm gonna go.
And... I'm gonna take my share.
You can have the rest.
If you keep moving, I'll shoot.
You're not gonna shoot
an unarmed man.
In the back.
You're not a killer.
Stop!
I'm gonna go down on
my knees, okay?
Don't move.
I'm just gonna go down on
my knees.
- I mean it!
- Okay.
Just relax.
I'm just gonna get down.
I'm not gonna move.
I'm right here. Okay?
Okay?
Just be cool.
Don't move!
Is it done?
Yeah.
It's done.
Sophie.
You want your cut? Or not?
You earned it.
Shit, I'm not even mad.
You killed it tonight.
Don't be scared.
I told you already,
you are not a witness.
You are my partner.
Whether you like it or not.
Are you worried?
Sophie.
You are worried about the cops.
Okay. You know what?
I'm gonna make a call
to the cops.
9-1-1 emergency response.
Hello, 911. Hello.
You gotta come.
Six Golden Lane.
There's dead bodies.
You gotta send someone.
Oh, my God!
We have cars on route, sir.
They're about five minutes out.
Hurry. Hurry. Oh, my God.
I'm hiding, I'm hiding,
I'm hiding.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Sir, stay on the...
My tracks are covered.
They can't pin any of
these guys on me.
Well, you made sure of that.
I was the reasonable one.
I just wanted to make
everything fair.
But, no, Debra.
She wanted to fuck me and
the government in the divorce.
Why do you think all this cash
isn't in a bank?
You can't steal
what's already stolen.
This is all ours now.
You and me, we're the only two
who know about this
in the whole world.
You can have
all my guys' shares.
All of it!
There's two million bucks!
You gotta tell me if
we're gonna split this
when the heat dies down.
You gotta tell me right now!
Are you in?
Or are you out?
There's my answer.
Oh, what a mistake, baby.
Sophie.
Where are you?
Redial.
No, no, no!
Straighten out.
Keep going.
Okay, a turn is coming up
to the left.
- To the left.
- Yeah. Yeah.
To the left. Straighten out.
That's it.
What is it?
After four days, I forgot
the world didn't
smell like sanitizer.
Do you mind, uh, taking me
the rest of the way?
Yeah, of course.
Can I have my backpack?
Sure.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Thought you would have
pulled out a cigarette by now.
Can't smoke anymore.
Bad for my training.
What?
I emailed Paralympics back.
I should be able to walk
in a week, so...
I want to be
back on the hill in six,
before the season ends.
Well, you're gonna need
new skis, then.
Your gear's almost
four years old now.
Just have to figure out how to
cover the training costs.
Too bad you didn't get a tip
this time, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, there you are.
Hey.
How's the picture?
Uh... whoa.
Hey, what happened
to the beginner hill?
Thought it was
time for the real thing.
You know, Sophie,
if you're not up to this,
you definitely
don't have to do it.
You thought I came up here
just for the view?
Do you need me to do anything?
- I told you I'd never...
- Kelly, it's fine.
Just enjoy the ride, okay?
I'm gonna have this guy
in my ear.
Cam, Kelly. Kelly, Cam.
Don't worry, Kelly.
She was always the better skier.
She'll probably just ignore me
and beat me to the bottom,
anyways.
I can believe that.
Okay.
Mic check.
Good, check.
Whenever you're ready.
- Hey, Sophie.
- Yeah.
Breathe.